<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim Christie</title>
    <link>http://tim-christie.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tim Christie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 22:19:49 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tim-christie.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 11</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171224/china-day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 22:19:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171224/china-day-11/</guid>
      <description>Ate a selection of items from Mr. Bao for breakfast this morning at the hotel, then packed up and checked out. Took a taxi to a Desheng Hotel and checked in.
Went out to eat lunch at a local restaurant specialising in Peking Duck.
Stopped by a bank on the way back to the hotel to try and resolve an ongoing issue with performing balance checks online.
Got in a taxi and travelled to the 798 Art Zone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 10</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171223/china-day-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 22:36:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171223/china-day-10/</guid>
      <description>Started the day with a quick breakfast of the buns we brought from Mr. Bao the night before, then headed off to the Beixinqiao metro station to find a Hainan Airlines store in the city as we needed to change our flight dates.
Arrived a Xidan station, and went to find the store. Unfortunately, the entire building it was supposed to be in was in the process of being demolished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 9</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171222/china-day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 23:03:36 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171222/china-day-9/</guid>
      <description>Woke up early before sunrise and got some rice noodles for breakfast from a local shop down the street. Saw a lot of construction workers going home, before the rest of the city wakes up.
Went back to the hotel and checked out, then caught a bus to the CBD - and transferred to the metro until Changsha South Railway Station. Boarded the high-speed train, and departed at 9am.
Arrived at the Beijing West Railway Station 5 hours and 39 minutes later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 8</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171221/china-day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 22:54:11 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171221/china-day-8/</guid>
      <description>At wontons for breakfast this morning. Booked some train tickets for our trip to Beijing tomorrow, and went to collect them from the Changsha South Railway Station via the city metro. There was quite a long queue so we had to wait for a while - but it was good to avoid having to do this tomorrow morning instead.
Afterwards, returned via metro to Yingwanzhen Station - and found lunch in a nearby fast food restaurant on Lushan Road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 7</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171220/china-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 22:33:19 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171220/china-day-7/</guid>
      <description>Ate blue corn and an egg for breakfast. Went out afterwards and caught a bus to the Hunan Martyr&amp;rsquo;s Park, Changsha&amp;rsquo;s largest park.
Saw the monument at the top of the hill, and walked around the side of a lake inside the park.
Afterwards, we walked to a nearby restaurant and ate a traditional Hunan style lunch.
Following lunch, we walked to the Hunan Provincial Museum and took a look around inside (no photos allowed).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 6</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171219/china-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 21:54:40 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171219/china-day-6/</guid>
      <description>Ate rice noodles for breakfast, and for lunch stir-fry tofu and vegetables. Went out to explore Juzhou Park in the afternoon. The park exists on an island in the middle of the Xiangjiang River (connected to the adjacent shorelines by a large bridge).
The island is about 6km long in total, we walked up and down a 2km stretch of this passing a number of interesting sights on the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 5</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171218/china-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 09:23:09 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171218/china-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Ate a buffet breakfast at the hotel this morning, then walked north past Hongshan metro station to find a bank which we had passed yesterday. Unfortunately, they were unable to help us - so we took a taxi to a larger bank a short distance away. After we were done, another taxi ride back to the MeiJing hotel - where we packed up our bags and checked out.
Hotel provided a free taxi to the Shenzhen North Railway Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 4</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171217/china-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 11:20:40 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171217/china-day-4/</guid>
      <description>This morning we returned to the Changsha-style rice noodle shop for breakfast. It is becoming noticeably more cold now, as opposed to temperatures comparable to Brisbane when we first arrived in Shenzhen.
Walked north of Hongshan station to find a bank, but arrived and discovered that they were closed. Continued on to shopping mall a block to the east, and ate lunch at a steamed fish restaurant.
After eating, walked back to Hongshan station and caught the metro to Dafen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 3</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171216/china-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 23:06:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171216/china-day-3/</guid>
      <description>This morning we returned to the local community area to find breakfast at a small Wonton shop we had walked past the night before. Went back to the MeiJing Hotel after eating and renewed our room for another night.
Walked to the Hongshan metro station &amp;amp; then back to the hotel. Ate a room service rice noodle meal for lunch.
Took the metro in the afternoon to Lianhua North, and walked over to the Lianhaushan Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 2</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171215/china-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 15:31:08 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171215/china-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Woke up and ate at the buffet breakfast inside the hotel. Proceeded to head out and search for a China Unicom store to acquire some SIM cards. Located the local store, however, they were not open (contrary to the business hours posted on the door).
The hotel was unable to renew the room we were staying in for another night, so we moved to the MeiJing Hotel in the Minzhi Residential District.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 1</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171214/china-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 15:21:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20171214/china-day-1/</guid>
      <description>I will be attempting to keep a travel log during our trip to China this year. This will likely be notes taken on-the-fly,and thus will be ordinarily kept quite brief.
We boarded Hainan Airlines flight HU412 in Brisbane at 11:00am, and departed at approximately 11:30am. Arrived in Shenzhen about 8 hours and 40 minutes later at roughly 6:10pm (local time).
Taxi drived took the &amp;ldquo;scenic route&amp;rdquo; to the hotel, however we called him out and paid a fair price for the trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akiyama Mio Watercolour</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161028/akiyama-mio-watercolour/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 22:00:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161028/akiyama-mio-watercolour/</guid>
      <description> Akiyama Mio &amp;mdash; Copyright &amp;copy; Kakifurai
Pencil sketch, inked lineart, and watercoloured.
 Arttec Como Sketch Pad (210gsm) Pentel Twist-Erase 0.5 mechanical pencil Zebra G-Pen Nib (Titanium) Windsor &amp;amp; Newton Black Ink  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misaka Mikoto Watercolour</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161027/misaka-mikoto-watercolour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 22:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161027/misaka-mikoto-watercolour/</guid>
      <description> Misaka Mikoto &amp;mdash; Copyright &amp;copy; Kazuma Kamachi &amp;amp; Kiyotaka Haimura
Pencil sketch, inked lineart, then watercoloured.
 Windsor &amp;amp; Newton A5 Visual Diary (110gsm) Pentel Twist-Erase 0.5 mechanical pencil Zebra G-Pen Nib (Titanium) Sailor Black Ink Koh-I-Noor Hardtmuth watercolours  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misaka Mikoto Sketch</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161026/misaka-mikoto-sketch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 22:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161026/misaka-mikoto-sketch/</guid>
      <description> Misaka Mikoto &amp;mdash; Copyright &amp;copy; Kazuma Kamachi &amp;amp; Kiyotaka Haimura
Pencil sketch and inked lineart.
 Windsor &amp;amp; Newton A5 Visual Diary (110gsm) Pentel Twist-Erase 0.5 mechanical pencil Zebra G-Pen Nib (Titanium) Sailor Black Ink  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chihiro Ohino Watercolour</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161025/chihiro-ohino-watercolour/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 23:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161025/chihiro-ohino-watercolour/</guid>
      <description> Cihiro Ohino &amp;mdash; Copyright &amp;copy; Hayao Miyazaki
Pencil sketch, inked lineart, erased, then watercoloured.
 Windsor &amp;amp; Newton A5 Visual Diary (110gsm) Pentel Twist-Erase 0.5 mechanical pencil Sailor 1911s H-F fountain pen Sailor Black Ink Koh-I-Noor Hardtmuth watercolours  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chihiro Ohino Sketch</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161024/chihiro-ohino-sketch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 22:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161024/chihiro-ohino-sketch/</guid>
      <description> Cihiro Ohino &amp;mdash; Copyright &amp;copy; Hayao Miyazaki
Pencil sketch, inked lineart, then erased.
 Windsor &amp;amp; Newton A5 Visual Diary (110gsm) Pentel Twist-Erase 0.5 mechanical pencil Sailor 1911s H-F fountain pen Sailor Black Ink  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bash on Ubuntu on Windows</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161023/bash-on-ubuntu-on-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 17:55:51 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161023/bash-on-ubuntu-on-windows/</guid>
      <description>I decided to spend some time updating my website over the weekend. Usually this would mean jumping on my Arch Linux machine &amp;mdash; however, I decided it would be a good chance to give Bash on Ubuntu on Windows a go and see how far I could get.
To my surprise, this went remarkably well.
With access to the Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL), and the Ubuntu package repositories (via apt-get), I had no issues at all downloading and configuring any of the software I needed to work on this site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrated to Hugo</title>
      <link>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161022/migrated-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 22:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim-christie.com/post/20161022/migrated-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Decided it was time to update this site. It&amp;rsquo;s still hosted on Github Pages, but is now using the Hugo static site generator.
So far so good. I&amp;rsquo;ve opted to use the Cactus Theme by digitalcraftsman, which has made setting this up a breeze.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>