<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tim Christie</title>
    <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tim Christie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 22:31:08 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tim-christie.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 26</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180108/china-day-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 22:31:08 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180108/china-day-26/</guid>
      <description>Technically not in China on the 26 day of these blog posts - but rather somewhere in the skies between there and Australia.
Touched down in Brisbane at about 10am AEST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 25</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180107/china-day-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 22:08:32 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180107/china-day-25/</guid>
      <description>Got up rather early today, and went to eat rice noodles for breakfast in a noodle shop a short ways down the road from the hotel we were staying at.
Finalised packing up all of our bags, then checked out of the hotel and bussed to Wuyi Square station where we caught the metro to Changsha South Railway Station.
From there, we caught a high-speed train back to Shenzhen North Railway Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 24</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180106/china-day-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 17:22:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180106/china-day-24/</guid>
      <description>Ate breakfast at a close by rice noodle shop (a couple of doors down from the hotel).
Started to organise our things in the morning, ready for the trip back to Australia tomorrow.
Ate a light lunch of tofu and vegetables.
Spent most of the afternoon indoors to avoid the cooler weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 23</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180105/china-day-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 16:58:12 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180105/china-day-23/</guid>
      <description>Got up and ate a quick breakfast at a rice noodle shop just down the road from the hotel, then visited a nearby cinema to watch the 2017 film &amp;ldquo;Youth&amp;rdquo;.
I thought the cinematography was rather good, and the story was entertaining. Luckily for me they ran it with English subtitles.
After the movie, we ate lunch in a Pizza Hut restaurant. The food was unlike what I am used to, but was an interesting experience none the less.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 22</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180104/china-day-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 21:44:01 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180104/china-day-22/</guid>
      <description>Got up and ate rice noodles for breakfast. It rained pretty much all day, so we spent most of the day indoors. Ate hotpot for lunch, and took a short walk in the afternoon. It&amp;rsquo;s become noticeably colder since we were last in Changsha, really feels like winter has properly set in now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 21</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180103/china-day-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 22:54:47 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180103/china-day-21/</guid>
      <description>Had breakfast at the same place again this morning, then checked out of the hotel and caught a taxi to the Hangzhou Railway Station to catch a high speed train back to Changsha.
The trip to Changsha took about 4 hours. After arriving, we took the metro to Wuyi Square and transferred to a bus to take us back to Yinpenling Residential District. We are staying at a different hotel this time, just a block down the road from the one we were at last time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 20</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180102/china-day-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 20:32:21 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180102/china-day-20/</guid>
      <description>Ate a quick breakfast this morning of soy milk, tea boiled eggs, and youtiao - before heading off to catch a bus to Feilai Peak.
Feilai Peak houses a collection of 330 statues carved into the cliffs and caves on the peak. We walked up to the top of the peak, taking a look at the carvings as we went.
There are also a number of Buddhist temples on the peak, which we spent some time walking through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 19</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180101/china-day-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 23:48:18 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20180101/china-day-19/</guid>
      <description>Ate a free buffet breakfast again in the hotel in Xitangzhen, then packed up our bags and walked to the bus station to travel back to Hangzhou. The bus was about an hour quicker on the way back than it had been to arrive in Xitangzhen. Caught the metro to Ding&amp;rsquo;an Road Station.
We checked back into the Merchant Marco Edgelake Hotel again in Hangzhou, and then went out to eat lunch at the nearby fast food restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 18</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171231/china-day-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 21:13:27 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171231/china-day-18/</guid>
      <description>Got up early this morning and took advantage of a free buffet breakfast which was provided by the hotel. The food was good so we ate a lot, as we were planning to be out for a while today.
After breakfast, we went directly to the Jiashan Xitang Ancient Town Scenic Area. We had a bit of trouble collecting the tickets, where the people selling them and the people checking the tickets at the gate had quite different ideas of what we needed to do to gain entry into the theme park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 17</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171230/china-day-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 18:59:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171230/china-day-17/</guid>
      <description>Ate a quick breakfast this morning at the same nearby Hangzhou-style local restaurant we ate at last night. On the way back to the hotel we passed a fruit store, and brought 2 freshly squeezed orange juices for ¥33, and some apples.
Checked out of the hotel, and caught the metro to 客运中心 where we transferred to a long distance bus station. Brought some tickets to Xitangzhen (西塘镇), but the next available seats were on a bus which departed in 2 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 16</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171229/china-day-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 20:10:44 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171229/china-day-16/</guid>
      <description>Ate a breakfast of tea-boiled eggs, pumpkin congee, soy milk, and youtiao in a nearly local Hangzhou restaurant.
Afterwards, we went for walk around the West Lake in a northerly direction.
Got as far as the island near Beili Lake, before we had to turn back towards the hotel to check out.
Moved to another hotel a short walk away, called Hangzhou Renhe Hotel. Went to get some lunch afterwards at a fast food restaurant called Old Uncle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 15</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171228/china-day-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 18:42:30 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171228/china-day-15/</guid>
      <description>The night on the overnight coach went quickly enough, woke up early and recharged our phones (limited charging stations available). Brought some congee (粥) and mantou (饅頭) for breakfast on the train.
The train arrived at 9am sharp. Disembarked at Hangzhou Railway Station (杭州), and took the metro from Chengzhan (城站) to Ding&amp;rsquo;an Road (定安路). Walked the rest of the way to the Merchant Marco Edgelake Hotel (on GuoHuo Road).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 14</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171227/china-day-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 18:32:13 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171227/china-day-14/</guid>
      <description>Woke up and ate at the nearby local-style fast food shop, then returned to the hotel and checked out.
We travelled into the city via bus to visit a hotpot restaurant that had good reviews. The restaurant was pretty close to the area we ate Nanjing-style food the night before. Unfortunately, it didn&amp;rsquo;t quite live up to the hype for us, and felt a little overpriced for what we got.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 13</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171226/china-day-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 22:56:27 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171226/china-day-13/</guid>
      <description>At some buns from Mr. Bao for breakfast in the hotel, then walked to a bus station just south of Anhuaqiao station.
Disembarked near Tiananmen Square, and walked over to the National Museum of China. There was a huge queue to get through an initial security check to enter the precinct, then another queue where we had to drop off our backpack. Getting tickets was pretty quick, as was moving through the final security checkpoint to enter the museum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 12</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171225/china-day-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 13:02:48 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171225/china-day-12/</guid>
      <description>Ate breakfast at the same nearby fast food restaurant we went to for dinner at last night. It was pretty cold outside, a temperature of 5 degrees Celsius is the forecast maximum.
Renewed the hotel booking for another night, and caught up on a few things in the hotel room..
Today we decided to go and take a look at a proper hutong. Walked to the nearby metro station (Anhuaqiao), and travelled to the Nanlouguxiang hutong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 11</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171224/china-day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 22:19:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171224/china-day-11/</guid>
      <description>Ate a selection of items from Mr. Bao for breakfast this morning at the hotel, then packed up and checked out. Took a taxi to a Desheng Hotel and checked in.
Went out to eat lunch at a local restaurant specialising in Peking Duck.
Stopped by a bank on the way back to the hotel to try and resolve an ongoing issue with performing balance checks online.
Got in a taxi and travelled to the 798 Art Zone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 10</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171223/china-day-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 22:36:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171223/china-day-10/</guid>
      <description>Started the day with a quick breakfast of the buns we brought from Mr. Bao the night before, then headed off to the Beixinqiao metro station to find a Hainan Airlines store in the city as we needed to change our flight dates.
Arrived a Xidan station, and went to find the store. Unfortunately, the entire building it was supposed to be in was in the process of being demolished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 9</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171222/china-day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 23:03:36 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171222/china-day-9/</guid>
      <description>Woke up early before sunrise and got some rice noodles for breakfast from a local shop down the street. Saw a lot of construction workers going home, before the rest of the city wakes up.
Went back to the hotel and checked out, then caught a bus to the CBD - and transferred to the metro until Changsha South Railway Station. Boarded the high-speed train, and departed at 9am.
Arrived at the Beijing West Railway Station 5 hours and 39 minutes later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 8</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171221/china-day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 22:54:11 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171221/china-day-8/</guid>
      <description>At wontons for breakfast this morning. Booked some train tickets for our trip to Beijing tomorrow, and went to collect them from the Changsha South Railway Station via the city metro. There was quite a long queue so we had to wait for a while - but it was good to avoid having to do this tomorrow morning instead.
Afterwards, returned via metro to Yingwanzhen Station - and found lunch in a nearby fast food restaurant on Lushan Road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 7</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171220/china-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 22:33:19 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171220/china-day-7/</guid>
      <description>Ate blue corn and an egg for breakfast. Went out afterwards and caught a bus to the Hunan Martyr&amp;rsquo;s Park, Changsha&amp;rsquo;s largest park.
Saw the monument at the top of the hill, and walked around the side of a lake inside the park.
Afterwards, we walked to a nearby restaurant and ate a traditional Hunan style lunch.
Following lunch, we walked to the Hunan Provincial Museum and took a look around inside (no photos allowed).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 6</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171219/china-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 21:54:40 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171219/china-day-6/</guid>
      <description>Ate rice noodles for breakfast, and for lunch stir-fry tofu and vegetables. Went out to explore Juzhou Park in the afternoon. The park exists on an island in the middle of the Xiangjiang River (connected to the adjacent shorelines by a large bridge).
The island is about 6km long in total, we walked up and down a 2km stretch of this passing a number of interesting sights on the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 5</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171218/china-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 09:23:09 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171218/china-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Ate a buffet breakfast at the hotel this morning, then walked north past Hongshan metro station to find a bank which we had passed yesterday. Unfortunately, they were unable to help us - so we took a taxi to a larger bank a short distance away. After we were done, another taxi ride back to the MeiJing hotel - where we packed up our bags and checked out.
Hotel provided a free taxi to the Shenzhen North Railway Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 4</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171217/china-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 11:20:40 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171217/china-day-4/</guid>
      <description>This morning we returned to the Changsha-style rice noodle shop for breakfast. It is becoming noticeably more cold now, as opposed to temperatures comparable to Brisbane when we first arrived in Shenzhen.
Walked north of Hongshan station to find a bank, but arrived and discovered that they were closed. Continued on to shopping mall a block to the east, and ate lunch at a steamed fish restaurant.
After eating, walked back to Hongshan station and caught the metro to Dafen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 3</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171216/china-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 23:06:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171216/china-day-3/</guid>
      <description>This morning we returned to the local community area to find breakfast at a small Wonton shop we had walked past the night before. Went back to the MeiJing Hotel after eating and renewed our room for another night.
Walked to the Hongshan metro station &amp;amp; then back to the hotel. Ate a room service rice noodle meal for lunch.
Took the metro in the afternoon to Lianhua North, and walked over to the Lianhaushan Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 2</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171215/china-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 15:31:08 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171215/china-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Woke up and ate at the buffet breakfast inside the hotel. Proceeded to head out and search for a China Unicom store to acquire some SIM cards. Located the local store, however, they were not open (contrary to the business hours posted on the door).
The hotel was unable to renew the room we were staying in for another night, so we moved to the MeiJing Hotel in the Minzhi Residential District.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China: Day 1</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171214/china-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 15:21:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20171214/china-day-1/</guid>
      <description>I will be attempting to keep a travel log during our trip to China this year. This will likely be notes taken on-the-fly,and thus will be ordinarily kept quite brief.
We boarded Hainan Airlines flight HU412 in Brisbane at 11:00am, and departed at approximately 11:30am. Arrived in Shenzhen about 8 hours and 40 minutes later at roughly 6:10pm (local time).
Taxi drived took the &amp;ldquo;scenic route&amp;rdquo; to the hotel, however we called him out and paid a fair price for the trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bash on Ubuntu on Windows</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20161023/bash-on-ubuntu-on-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 17:55:51 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20161023/bash-on-ubuntu-on-windows/</guid>
      <description>I decided to spend some time updating my website over the weekend. Usually this would mean jumping on my Arch Linux machine &amp;mdash; however, I decided it would be a good chance to give Bash on Ubuntu on Windows a go and see how far I could get.
To my surprise, this went remarkably well.
With access to the Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL), and the Ubuntu package repositories (via apt-get), I had no issues at all downloading and configuring any of the software I needed to work on this site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrated to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://tim-christie.com/post/20161022/migrated-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 22:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tim-christie.com/post/20161022/migrated-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Decided it was time to update this site. It&amp;rsquo;s still hosted on Github Pages, but is now using the Hugo static site generator.
So far so good. I&amp;rsquo;ve opted to use the Cactus Theme by digitalcraftsman, which has made setting this up a breeze.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>